Our environments can affect the way we feel.
我们所处的环境会影响我们的情绪。
This is not a new concept – after all, the traditional practice of feng shui has been with us for thousands of years.
这并非一个全新的概念——毕竟，风水这一传统做法已经伴随我们数千年之久。
More recently, scientific research concluded that the design of healthcare environments could support patients in their recovery.
近期，科学研究得出结论，医疗环境的设计能够辅助患者康复。
Increasingly, however, it is our homes that are being seen as places we can improve our wellness.
而如今，我们的家也越来越被视作能够提升我们身心健康的场所。
A new approach to interior design suggests that many of us now care less about how our homes look and more about how they make us feel.
一种全新的室内设计理念提出，如今我们中的许多人不再那么在意家的外观，反而更关注家带给我们的感受。
How we feel can be influenced by a number of different things, including the furniture and objects within our homes and how these are arranged.
我们的情绪会受到诸多不同因素的影响，包括家中的家具和物品，以及它们的摆放方式。
For example, 'to create cosiness and the ability to connect with others, we want our furniture facing each other', says Lindsay T Graham, a personality and social psychologist.
例如，人格与社会心理学家林赛·T·格雷厄姆说：“为了营造温馨感，创造与他人建立联结的氛围，我们会把家具面对面摆放。”
Smaller objects, too, have a lot of power, according to Monica Khemsurov, one of the founders of online design magazine Sight Unseen.
线上设计杂志《未见之物》的创始人之一莫妮卡·凯姆苏罗夫认为，小摆件同样拥有巨大的力量。
Whether it's something an old friend made for us or a souvenir purchased while travelling, objects allow us to relive moments or feel closer to people we love at a glance.
无论是老朋友为我们亲手做的物件，还是旅行时买的纪念品，这些物品都能让我们在一瞥之间重温过往时光，或是与所爱之人拉近距离。
It makes sense, therefore, that taking a more intentional approach to where we place objects in our home, can affect our mood.
因此，更有目的性地摆放家中物品是明智的选择，因为这会影响我们的情绪。
Other elements that help create a personal space that makes you feel good include the type of lighting, the use of colour and texture, as well as bringing nature into the home.
其他有助于打造令人愉悦的私人空间的要素，还包括灯光类型、色彩与材质的运用，以及将自然元素引入家中。
Plants and 'natural materials, particularly unpainted wood, are really great for keeping our stress levels in check', says environmental psychologist Sally Augustin.
环境心理学家萨莉·奥古斯丁说：“绿植和天然材料，尤其是未上漆的木材，非常有助于控制我们的压力水平。”
And controlling stress levels can also be helped by making sure our work space and any clutter are hidden from sight when we want to feel calm, for example, during our night-time routine before going to bed.
而当我们想要获得平静时，比如在睡前的夜间常规流程中，确保工作区域和所有杂物都不在视线范围内，也有助于我们控制压力水平。
However we choose to adjust our living spaces to improve wellness, the final tip from the experts is to not treat our homes as a museum.
无论我们选择如何调整居住空间来提升身心健康，专家给出的最终建议是，不要把家当成一座博物馆。
Instead, we should see them as idiosyncratic and constantly changing – just like us.
相反，我们应该把家看作是独具个人特色、且不断变化的空间——就像我们自己一样。